Scott Hatfield

Experienced and widely skilled software developer with numerous published software packages and mobile applications.

270 E Richards Road Oregon, WI 53575 (608) 921-3540

contact@hatfieldscott.com

Portfolio: https://hatfieldscott.com

EDUCATION

UW Milwaukee — BS in Information Science and Technology

Graduated JULY 2015

My academic efforts towards earning my degree in information science and technology combined computer science, programming, communication, and information architecture coursework.

RELATED EXPERIENCE

Sub-Zero Group, Fitchburg, WI — *Mobile Application Developer*

MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

As part of an interdisciplinary team of engineers and developers, worked to develop, test, maintain, and deploy mobile applications and internal software tools designed to support the company's IoT infrastructure, manufacturing feedback systems, and customer service operations.

UW Madison, Madison, WI — Sitefinity CMS Developer

FEBRUARY 2012 - AUGUST 2014

Collaborated with developers and academic faculty to deploy a new web presence and content management system for departments within the School of Education. This included work on optimizing sites for usage on mobile devices and preparing training material.

EETech, Boise ID (Remote) — *Content Contributor*

NOVEMBER 2018 - MARCH 2020

Wrote numerous articles and tutorials about a **wide variety of technology products**, including those involving existing or bespoke software packages.

OVERVIEW

As an experienced software developer with strong analytical and problem-solving skills I have published numerous software packages that interact with a wide range of technologies and use several programming languages and tools. I have professional and educational experience allowing me to bring not only technical skills but also business acumen to the software engineering process.

PUBLISHED MOBILE APPLICATIONS

Sub-Zero Group Field App

In my role at Sub-Zero Group I have developed several service tools and mobile apps from scratch. The "Field App" is a cross-platform mobile application that allows appliance service technicians to conduct diagnostics wirelessly and leverage machine learning models to make faster and more accurate assessments and repairs.

Sub-Zero Group Owner's App

As a mobile developer at Sub-Zero Group, one of my other responsibilities is maintaining the app used by appliance owners to interact with their appliances and to prepare the app to support new products.

Blue Paint: Bluetooth Visualization

Blue Paint is an app allowing the visualization of Bluetooth signal strength. The app uses a series of colored dots which, when captured in a long-exposure photograph, visually indicate the strength of a Bluetooth signal.